Wait. listen.
What if we split the money. huh?
The sun always shines after the storm!
The hell?
I miss you through to my bones!
Insolent peasant! Unhand me!
I am your king. and you will do as I say!
- Is that...?
- Fletcher Demming.
- The real estate baron?
- I saw him at a party a few months ago.
He seemed perfectly fine.
- Now he's locked up in Arkham.
- Arkham?
He can afford better treatment than that.
No. Apparently. a few weeks ago.
he donated his entire fortune to charity.
He always seemed like such a selfish man.
Perhaps I was wrong.
You weren't.
There's something more going on here.
Fine! Fine! I'll do it!
I'll give it all up.
I'll give everything away. Everything!
Stop.
Is that a promise?
I... I promise.
On my life. On my life. I promise.
I don't believe you.
No. no!
No!
I don't know.
Sometimes.
I just feel so hopeless about this city.
Like it's past the point of saving.
- You've got to learn to laugh it off.
- Is that your professional opinion?
You would not believe the things
I hear in my sessions. Barbie.
All the greed and corruption
and inhumanity my patients spew.
So many nights I'd go home feeling
just like you do now.
- And laughing helps?
- That. and...
Saw you two outside. Mind if I join?
- Hey. lady cop.
- Oh. hey.
You're not returning my calls.
I've been meaning to. Sorry.
I'm worried about your dad.
Ever since the mayor put Flass and Bullock
in charge of the task force.
it's like he's trying to prove something.
He can't keep pushing himself like this.
Will you talk to him?
I can try.
but I really wouldn't know what to say.
- Let's role play.
- No.
Fine. Geez.
Look. Renee. my dad's
the strongest man I know. He'll be okay.
I hope you're right.
Keep your chin up. Barbie.
Gotham needs you.
It's sweet the way you worry
about the commissioner.
Her dad's more of a father to me
than mine ever was.
Hm... I think we should have dinner.
- Oh?
- Somewhere spiffy. My treat.
- How's tomorrow night?
- Um. yeah. I can make that work.
Good. Then it's a date.
Come out with your hands up!
Don't let him escape.
Ah!
He's not here!
They're chattel.
And now they want to unionize.
After everything I've done for them.
You're frustrated.
Damn right I'm frustrated.
I don't deserve this.
They're worse than my children.
That's time.
I gotta say. Doc. I feel like
my blood pressure just dropped 20 points.
I don't know what kind of magic you work.
but these sessions.
they are really helping.
I'm glad you feel that way. but I don't.
I don't think
we're making any progress at all.
Hey! What is this?
You're a real menace to society. Emerson.
I've tried to get you to see the humanity
in your employees. in your family.
But nothing is getting through.
I think it's time
to ratchet things up a bit.
How's our patient doing this morning?
I-I can't. I can't write anymore. Please...
Now. now.
If you're not bleeding.
you're not working hard enough.
Isn't that what you said to your son?
I'll make you pay. you piece of...
That's 10.000 more lines. Mr. Moorehouse.
There is no bad bulb.
I'm the bad bulb.
I assure you.
there's one in there. Mr. Smith.
Keep looking.
I'm not eating that.
and you can't make me!
- Is that so. Mr. Belsky?
- I want dessert!
Such a child.
But that was always your problem.
What is this? Where am I?
Welcome to my inpatient facility.
Mr. Collins.
I call it the Playpen.
This is kidnapping.
I'll have your head on a spike for this.
The tables have turned. Mr. Collins.
The kings don't run this court anymore.
The jester does.
Hastings?
Please release Mr. Belsky from his cell.
What's going on?
Belsky. would you like some dessert?
Yes.
Get Mr. Collins
to give up all his earthly possessions.
and you can have all the pudding you want.
- I don't have to eat my beans first?
- Not today.
Mm... pudding.
I found another one. sir.
Jorge Campos. the shipping tycoon.
Died three years ago. penniless.
Two weeks before his death.
he donated everything he owned
to women's shelters across the city.
- How did he die?
- Car crash. Drove right into a tree.
Who would be able to convince
some of Gotham's greediest men
to give away
all their worldly possessions?
Maybe their psychiatrist.
Mr. Demming? I'm Barbara Gordon.
I've been appointed by the court
to represent you.
How much do you charge?
I'm a public defender.
The city pays my salary.
Good. because I'm all out of money.
Money and time.
Can you help me get out of here?
Everyone in this place is crazy.
First they'll need to determine
if you're a threat to yourself or others.
Mr. Demming.
Stop calling me that! "Mister."
- I'm a pharaoh!
- Okay.
I think we better get
an independent psych evaluation
before we put you in front of a judge.
I have a friend. Dr. Harleen Quinzel.
who'd probably do it for...
Harley Quinn?
- Do you know her?
- I don't know. I...
Her name feels so good in my mouth.
Five minute warning. Miss Gordon.
Mr. Demming. wait!
Runner! Lockdown! Lockdown!
- Oh!
- Stop him! Watch out!
Stop!
I'm coming!
Get off of me! I want to see her!
I need to be with her!
See who? Who do you want to see?
- Miss Gordon. you okay?
- I'm fine. Just restrain him.
Tell me her name!
Ha... Ha...
- Harleen.
- Barbie!
I was hoping I'd run into you here.
You'll never guess
who I'm having dinner with tonight.
Do you know a man named Fletcher Demming?
- Name sounds familiar.
- The real estate mogul.
Oh. yeah. Why do you ask?
He's a new client. Needs a psych eval.
But he seemed to recognize your name.
Hmm. Well. I don't know why that would be.
I don't know him personally.
So. anyway. I asked out Renee.
I was so suave. You would have been proud.
- Oh. that's great.
- So give me the skinny.
- What kind of food does she like?
- Well. I've run into her at Batyo's.
That joint? No.
I've gotta impress her.
make her think I'm classy.
Hey. Dad. Brought you some lunch.
Oh. thanks. Just set it over there.
How's it going?
Uh. the mayor seems to have forgotten
Batman isn't the only criminal
in this city.
I've got cases pouring in.
and the worst cops on the force
have commandeered all my people.
- Something on your mind?
- I'm...
I can't even say it.
What do you do
when the evidence is pointing you
in a direction you don't want to look?
The truth is always better
than the alternative.
At least then you can
do something about it.
- Renee thinks you need a day off.
- I know that.
- She has a point.
- Not gonna happen. kid.
Not interested.
What the hell?
Lied right to my face.
- May I help you?
- Yes.
I'm looking for the owner.
William Hastings.
- What's this regarding?
- It's personal.
I am William Hastings.
Oh. I'm so sorry. I didn't realize.
I'm representing Fletcher Demming.
and I know you were both patients
of Dr. Quinzel.
Isn't Dr. Quinzel's
client list confidential?
Listen. Mr. Hastings. my client
is suffering psychologically.
I checked your office.
and nobody's seen you in months.
- So I was worried that...
- This is a wild invasion of privacy.
I demand you leave
the property immediately.
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you trying
to break into William Hastings' house?
Why are you?
I think Dr. Quinzel
is brainwashing some of her patients.
- Do you have proof of that?
- Not yet.
Harleen's my friend.
If she's hurting people. I need to know.
Go back to the city. I'll handle Quinzel.
Wait!
That is not fair.
I bet you were an adorable figure skater.
Could you do those spinny things?
The spinny things were my specialty.
In fact. that's the technical name
for that move.
I'm kind of impressed you knew that.
Really? Wait.
that's not what it's really called!
No. not at all. But next time.
maybe I'll take you to the skating rink.
and I'll let you call them
whatever you want.
Next time. huh?
Guess I'm doing okay. then.
There's a call for Dr. Quinzel.
Excuse me. Yes?
I understand. I'll be right there.
I'm sorry.
- There's an emergency with a patient.
- Oh.
Tell you what. Meet me later at Hopper's
on Wilson and Lowery.
We'll pick up where we left off.
- Where is he?
- The Playpen. ma'am.
I knew you'd come for me.
I knew it when I profiled you
for the police.
I'm your type.
How many criminals do you have to catch
before you feel better. Batman?
Ten. 20?
Whoever nabs Batman
will make me very happy.
And whoever doesn't is dead.
Ah!
Look. I don't want to kill you.
But I need to give myself a head start.
so your hero complex
doesn't bite me in the heinie.
You've got a few minutes to figure
your way out before the house blows.
Quinzel...
Maybe next time we can unpack some
of that childhood trauma.
Oh. my God!
Batman!
- Are you going to miss Gotham. ma'am?
- Just drive.
Barbara.
Turn the car around.
- But...
- Now!
We gotta go. Barbie.
This place is gonna blow.
Harleen. what have you done?
I'll answer all your questions later.
but we gotta go now.
We're not leaving without him.
You damaged it.
No!
Come on!
Let me go. Barbie.
I can pull you up.
I'm not going to prison or Arkham.
Your friendship
with Dr. Quinzel made you reckless.
- You should have left when I...
- Shut up.
Just shut up.
I... have to go.
Yeah. I know.
I'm sorry.
- Hello?
- Hey. Renee. it's me.
I'm sorry I couldn't make it.
Where are you? Is everything okay?
I've gotta leave town for a while.
I'll look you up when I'm back.
I promise. Keep an eye on Barbie for me.
Okay?
- Harleen...
- Bye.